export const questions = [
    { question: "Rearrange: 'P E P A L'", answer: "APPLE" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'T C A'", answer: "CAT" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'O G D'", answer: "DOG" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'E R T E'", answer: "TREE" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'N U S'", answer: "SUN" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'T S R A'", answer: "STAR" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'T B R I'", answer: "BIRT" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'T R O I R'", answer: "ROTI" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'A B L L'", answer: "BALL" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'K O O B'", answer: "BOOK" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'A R C'", answer: "CAR" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'O N I L'", answer: "LION" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'F S I H'", answer: "FISH" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'H E U S O'", answer: "HOUSE" },
    { question: "Rearrange: 'G R E A'", answer: "GEAR" },
  ];
  